(Howard:)That's not true.
Howard, I'm doing laundry!
You want me to put anything in for you?!
There's some underwear in the hamper!
Oh, good, I got that new stain stick to try out!
(Howard:)Thank you.
I only put it on the list two weeks ago!
(Howard:)Okay, I see what you're getting at.
(Howard:)How about this weekend,
I'll box up all my things...
...and move them to our place?
(Howard:)Thank you.
The lightsabers will look great
in the living room.
(Bernadette:)Or in the closet. We can decide later.
Howard, help!
My hand's stuck in the garbage disposal!
Just let go of whatever piece of food
you're holding!
Are you kidding?!
It's a perfectly good chicken leg!
(Leonard:)Hey, look who's out after dark
like a big boy.
(Sheldon:)I was out raising heck
with Mr. Wil Wheaton.